# INES RADIC

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Web developer with extensive knowledge in front and back-end development. University of Oregon graduate with a bachelor's degree in General Science and a certificate in the university's Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp. I have newly developed skills in JavaScript, CSS, HTML, NodeJS, MongoDB, React and responsive web design using frameworks such as Bootstrap and Material-UI. Known as a highly motivated individual, I bring forth great communication skills with my extensive customer service experience, understanding of user needs with my marketing background, and overall passion for front-end development. I am excited to apply my skills and experience to a driven team and further my knowledge in web development.

## Links







LinkedIn: ines-radic

GitHub

Portfolio

## **PROJECTS**

### Music Spider | GitHub | Website

**Summary:** Using two APIs, the user can search parts of lyrics and the results will be the name of the artist and image, song name, link to lyrics, and three similar artists.

Role: CSS styling, responsive design, and Shazam API

functionality.

**Tools:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Materialize

## Weather Dashboard | GitHub | Website

**Summary:** Weather application that provides the current conditions for the user's searched city and the five-day forecast.

Role: Sole author

**Tools:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Materialize

Better Books | GitHub | Website

**Summary:** Book application that lets the user save a list

of books for future reading. Role: Front-end development

**Tools:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Materialize, Sequelize, Google Books, Node, Express, & MySQL

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Roseland Theater **Marketing Assistant**

2019-current Portland, OR

Assembled expense reports and invoices for concerts, managed social media presence, advertised upcoming shows, and reported ticket sales.

#### **Key Accomplishments:**

• Handled calendar for upcoming shows as well as communicated with agents after just 4 months with the theater.

Sunglass Hut **Key Holder** 

2017-2019 Portland, OR

Provided exceptional customer service, handled transactions, deposited and calculated daily sales reports.

#### **Key Accomplishments:**

• Promoted from sales associate to key-holder after 5 months with the company.

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of Oregon**

2020-2021

Portland, OR | Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

**University of Oregon** 

2014-2018

Eugene, OR | Bachelor of Science, General Science

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, React, CSS3, HTML5

**Applications:** GitHub

**Tools:** Node|S, Mongoose, Sequelize, ¡Query, Bootstrap,

Materialize, APIs.